Here's
the AI news you probably missed this
week. Starting with the brand new model
that has everybody talking right now,
Claude Fable 5. Now, this is a model
that I did an entire breakdown video of,
where I explain exactly what this model
is, what people love about it, what
people hate about it, some
misconceptions, and even test it a
little bit. You can find it over on my
YouTube channel. It's called Why
Everyone Is Freaking Out Mythos. At
least for right now. I split test titles
and thumbnails constantly. But in case
this is like the only video you watch
each week to stay up to date with the
news, I'll give you the TL didn't watch.
So, in Anthropic's announcement on June
9th, they actually announced two models,
Claude Fable 5 and Claude Mythos 5.
There's been a lot of videos and tweets
and things like that saying that
Anthropic finally unleashed mythos on
the world, but that's not technically
true. They call Claude Fable 5 a mythos
class model, but it's not actually the
mythos model that everybody was freaking
out about a couple months ago. This
Mythos class model sits at a tier above
Opus. So they have Haiku as their lowest
tier, fastest, cheapest models to use.
Sonnet was their middle tier. Opus was
their top tier. Now the Mythos tier is
the tier above Opus. And we're getting
Fable 5, which is a Mythos tier model.
The actual Mythos 5 model is for a small
group of cyber defenders and
infrastructure providers. They claim
it's the same underlying model as Fable
5, but with the safeguards lifted in
some areas. So there's a lot of extra
safeguards put on top of this fable 5
which prevents it from cyber security
related prompts, biology related
prompts, and even prompts related to
like training your own AI models.
Enthropic doesn't want anybody to use
their models to help them train their
own models, which is like a big point of
contention right now. If you're
interested in benchmarks, here's how it
stacks up against other models. It's
pretty much state-of-the-art in
everything if you trust these
benchmarks. Now, SweetBench Pro hard to
trust because it was recently found out
that a lot of the Claude models when
being tested for this benchmark
essentially looked up the answer key
instead of actually solving the problem.
Now, this model is really designed for
like the biggest, toughest, most logic
intense projects that you throw at it.
We can see here Fable and Mythos can
work autonomously for longer than any
previous Claude models. Now, the big
issue that people have with this model
is more the safety and security issues.
People have been showing screenshots
where they upload blood work to it and
ask it to analyze the blood work and it
refuses saying that it's not safe to do
that or people asking questions about
cancer. This is actually something I
confirmed myself when I asked it explain
how BRCA one mutations increase breast
cancer risk. I originally asked Fable 5
this prompt and it switched it to Opus
4.8 for me saying that it was too unsafe
to ask Fable. There was also some
controversy around this. like if you
were to ask it about LLM development, it
would actually pivot to like a dumber
model and not answer the questions for
you. This is from Anthropics
documentation. We've added safeguards
related to Frontier LLM development.
We've implemented new interventions that
limit Claude's effectiveness for
requests targeting Frontier LLM
development. Unlike our interventions
for cyber security, biology, and
chemistry, and distillation attempts,
these safeguards will not be visible to
the user. So essentially, if you were
asking this model to help you create
your own separate large language model,
it would still respond. It would just
dumb down the model and just give you
like a worse response than it should.
And people on X were not happy with
this. The CEO of Hugging Face said,
"Concentration of power, capabilities,
and economic wealth is the biggest risk
in AI. We need open science and open
source more than ever." Jeremy Howard
says, "Anthropic has chosen the opposite
of the safe path. They're allowing
themselves, the current top lab, to use
their top model for frontier AI
research. They've said they'll sabotage
others who try. This means the AI
frontier advances and power imbalance
increases. Graham Nubig here says, "I
feel we're getting a glimpse of a future
where AI is only provided to a
privileged few, and that's not a future
I want to live in." And there are many
such cases of tweets along this same
vein here. Luckily, however, Anthropic
relented sort of. According to this
article on NBC News here, after the
outcry, Anthropic backtracked and
reversed some of its most conservative
decisions less than 2 hours after Fable
5's release, highlighting growing
concerns about AI company's ability to
unilaterally limit users access to
helpful AI generated information. You
should have visibility into the
safeguards we have in place and why.
We're sorry for not getting the balance
right. Basically, what it sounds like is
happening is Entropic's still going to
block these things. they're still going
to send you to a dumber version of the
model when you ask them. They're just
going to tell you that they're doing it
instead of not telling you that they're
doing it. So, some quick additional
details here before actually showing you
some of the things it's capable of. As
of right now, you can use it inside of
one of the paid plans. So, Pro, Max, and
Team plans can use this Fable 5 model,
but only until June 22nd. On June 23rd,
they're going to remove Fable 5 from
those plans. And if you want to use it
after that, it's going to require
additional usage credits. They do say if
capacity allows, it'll extend the
included window, so maybe we'll get it
for a little bit longer. It is, however,
pretty much the most expensive model.
Pricing for both models is $10 per
million input tokens and $50 per million
output tokens. That's exactly double the
cost of Claude Opus 4.8. Now, saying all
of that, it is a really, really good
model, especially if you're using it for
like coding stuff. It's coded stuff with
one shot that just blew me away. In the
last video I made about it, I actually
gave it the prompt, make a clone of Mega
Bonk, which is, you know, a really fun
3D game. And it basically one-shotted
this game. And it looks really, really
good. I mean, this was the very, very
first iteration out of the box with only
that single prompt. I mean, it looks
more like a potato than an actual
person. And there's not much animation.
We're just getting cubes. But the game
was really fun. I was pretty impressed
with how it came out on the first try.
And it coded the whole thing into a
single HTML file, which is kind of
crazy, but I wasn't totally happy with
that first version. So, I went back and
forth with a few more prompts, maybe
four more prompts, giving it different
features and different things I wanted
to do with the graphics. And here's
where that game stands now that Fable
created. And yes, it even generated the
music. But we can see our character
walks around. I can actually rotate my
camera around the character. Our enemies
are a little bit uh better looking than
the cues we had before. There's actually
different depth to the terrain. There's,
you know, rocks and things that you can
bump into. I added a the ability to
sprint, the ability to jump. It's just a
much better game than the original
potato running around killing cubes. So,
I was really impressed with this. I even
put this game online if you want to try
it and play around with it for free. The
link will be in the description and I
put it up on GitHub. So, if you do want
to download this and fork it and make
your own version of it, it is available
to mess around with there. But I'm
warning you, it's pretty addicting game.
Just for fun, I asked Fable to make me a
YouTube clone called AI Tube. Not
because I wanted to see if it can clone
the look of the site, but I wanted to
actually see if it would clone a
recommendation algorithm. I wanted it to
pull a bunch of videos from YouTube and
then based on videos that I watched, it
actually recommend new videos. And this
is just one shot. This is one prompt
here. And this is what it looks like. As
you can see, this is AI tube. This is
not YouTube complete with history. You
can see I've already been testing it
where I watched a couple videos in the
history. There's an explore page with
hardware, podcasts, entertainment, all
again videos related to AI. And it's
showing a bunch of my videos because,
well, I watched one of my videos and
then it started recommending more of
those. If I come down here and watch,
you know, like one of Matt Vid Pro's
videos, you can see it looks just like
I'm watching it on YouTube. It's got
this sidebar with up next and
everything, but if I actually go home,
it should have updated my homepage. Now,
it's still recommending my videos
because it pulled in more of my videos
than any other videos. But we can see
that it no longer is recommending the
Matt Vid Pro video because it thinks I
already watched it. If I click on this
Wes Roth video and then click back to my
homepage, I actually have a slightly
updated set of videos. I don't know how
well the recommendation algorithm is
working. It's kind of hard for me to
test since it seemed to have pulled in a
lot of my own videos, but it seems like
it is updating. Every time I watch a
video and come back to the homepage, the
videos sort of change a little bit.
Anyway, it was a fun one prompt test. I
don't actually plan on pursuing this as
a real project, but probably the most
impressive project that I built is this
new one called YouTube Article B-roll
Generator. Now, this one actually lives
on my desktop. It doesn't live in the
browser, but let me show you what this
one does. You can see I can turn any
article into B-roll. I just give it a
URL. So, for example, I can give it this
article we were just looking at on
anthropic claude fable 5. But what I did
was I made it so I can highlight text
like this. Let's just say I want to
highlight for a small group of cyber
defenders and infrastructure providers
blah blah blah. I select that text.
Click save selection. And then maybe I
want to select some more text down here
about knowledge work. Select this
paragraph here. Click save selection at
the top. And then if I click capture
page, watch what happens. It actually
screenshots the entire page. And then it
gives me these animations automatically
out of the box where it zooms in on the
page for me and highlights the text I
just highlighted just like that. So it
highlighted that first chunk of text and
then it's going to zoom down and
highlight that second chunk of text that
I was talking about right there like
that. And I've made it have a bunch of
different animations. So I've got this
headline reveal. So this is the second
type of animation that it'll create
where it'll zoom in like that. And then
I've got this readalong animation where
it does it in this style. They're all
pretty similar, but you get the idea.
We've got a spotlight here where I press
play on this video. And you can see it
sort of spotlights it like that. Or this
box call out. You can see it zooms to
this and then sort of circles it. Yeah,
still some issues I got to figure out
here, but then it circles that paragraph
there. I can change how long each of
these steps last for. I can change the
color of the highlighting, change the
color of the borders, things like that.
And then when I'm done, I click on
export and it saves it as an MP4. And
now I've got B-roll of this article that
I can throw into my video. And I don't
have to go record this B-roll
separately. It just generated it for me.
Obviously, a very niche problem that
solves something that I do in my videos,
but it's going to save me a heck of a
lot of time. And this was done with two
prompts in Fable. All right, I want to
move on past Fable for now because I did
make a whole video about that. But there
was another huge event this week that
the AI world is buzzing about, and
that's Apple's WWDC event, their
worldwide developer conference event.
And this year, it was all about AI. So,
I'm going to quickly cover some of the
big AI announcements that came out of
WWDC. I'm going to do my best to sort of
rapid fire cover everything because
again, there was a lot. And I'm not
getting into like every single
announcement they got into, just the
sort of more practical AI stuff that I
think most people are going to care
about. They started by announcing that
they're actually going to be using their
own foundation models as well as
Google's Gemini models.
>> This year, we embarked on a deep
collaboration with Google, leveraging
the technologies behind their Gemini
family of models. Together, we created
the next generation of Apple Foundation
models for our integrated Apple
intelligence experiences. They explained
that when you use Siri AI on the phone,
it's either going to handle that AI
prompt on the phone directly or using
private clouds where Google gets none of
your data saved. They talked about how
Siri is going to have this personal
context understanding. So, it's going to
know your photos, your calendars, your
text messages. Pretty much anything that
developers give access to this context,
Siri's going to be able to use that. A
big chunk of this keynote was dedicated
to like the Siri that we kind of always
hoped Siri would be more capable. It has
access to world knowledge. It has access
to context on your phone. It's
supposedly going to be more
conversational. There's going to be a
dedicated Siri app. It's going to have
visual intelligence, so you can actually
open your camera and it will understand
what it sees around you as well as
what's on your photos. You're going to
be able to write with Siri. They showed
off some examples in their keynote where
they asked about tickets for a concert
and it told them they had to enter a
lottery and then he set a reminder to
enter the lottery at that time. He
showed it a picture on Instagram and
asked where it was and it looked at that
picture, figured out where it was and
then gave him directions to where that
was. You know, he was rearranging photos
by dictating to Siri. So, it sounds like
you're going to be operating your phone
by just sort of talking to it if you
want to do it that way. Hey, take this
photo, put it here. Hey, remind me about
this thing. Look at the photo on my
screen. Tell me where it is. Give me
directions to it. Like, they're just
trying to make this thing much more
conversational to go do things on your
behalf within your phone and the context
that it has on your phone. You'll be
able to customize your Siri, like how
fast it talks and how expressive it is.
There's various voices you can choose
from. You know, kind of the stuff that
you would expect from most of like an AI
chatbot these days. Here's a few more
examples of ways that they were using it
in their demo. They put together a plan
to visit different places in New York.
It reviewed the conversation and helped
them get back up to date with it. It
reviewed some financial data for them.
Again, a lot of what we've seen out of
tools like Chat GPT, like Anthropic,
like Gemini. It's a lot of the same kind
of stuff just now coming native to an
iPhone. Another thing I found kind of
interesting is if you're on like a Mac
or a MacBook, Siri is going to come to
Spotlight. So, you know, if you hit
command spacebar and bring up this
little spotlight search, you're going to
be able to prompt it with AI and say,
you know, rearrange these folders or
look at all of these documents and tell
me the differences between them, things
like that. And the built-in AI on device
will be able to do those kinds of things
for you. You can see he plugged in three
different like shed kits, selected them
all, and then asked for a comparison,
and then it popped up a little box where
it compared the three for him. This new
version of Siri is going to come to your
watch. It's going to come to the Apple
Vision Pro. You can see this little
bubble in this center of the screen
here. Essentially, if you want to use
Siri on your Apple Vision Pro, you just
look at the bubble. And because it's got
eyetracking, it sees that you're looking
at it. And when you talk to the bubble,
it, you know, does Siri stuff. And
because there's a new dedicated Siri
app, it sort of will save all of your
conversations and things you're doing in
that app. So, it works across device.
And theoretically, you'll have context
across device. So you can be doing
something on your phone or your watch,
your Apple Vision Pro, be sitting at
your computer later and ideally it will
have the context of what you were doing
on that other device earlier. They're
also adding a new Siri mode in the
camera app. So if you select Siri, then
it basically will use the context of
what the camera sees for whatever you
prompt it with. So in this picture,
they're pointing it at a red ball and
because they're in Siri mode, Siri
starts telling them this appears to be a
traditional cricket ball, etc. They're
able to highlight things on the screen
and ask Siri about those things. They
look at like a calendar on a web page
and it actually pulls in the event
separately. You know, here's them
talking to Siri in the Apple Vision Pro
about what they're seeing in the
browser. You can write with Siri, so
it'll actually help you write like a
rough draft. You know, it's a lot of the
same stuff we've kind of had access to
in almost all of the AI tools, just, you
know, now Apple's version. It'll give
you suggestions inside of mail based on
what it reads in the email. Now, out of
the entire keynote, this was the thing I
was probably the most excited about
actually getting on my phone is this
shortcuts feature with AI. You can
essentially describe the shortcut you
want, right? Like, if you're not
familiar with shortcuts, they're like
little automations that you can set on
your phone. Like, if I'm in a certain
location, send this text message to this
person. So, they're adding this feature
called describe a shortcut, which allows
you to use AI to say here's what I want
to happen. And it will actually go and
build that shortcut for you. Like you
just say, "When I'm leaving work,
message Pedro. I'm on my way with my
ETA." And it will actually go and build
that shortcut for you. I like never use
the shortcuts feature, but if I can just
like explain what I want it to do, and
it goes and automatically figures out
how to build that shortcut for me,
that'll be pretty cool. I think you're
going to be able to generate images with
AI. So, they gave it a picture of
somebody and said, "Make her holding a
cake." Then they said, "Give her a
detective outfit." And it generated the
same image, but with a detective outfit.
And then they selected the cake and said
add candles to the cake. And then of
course it generated an image with
candles on the cake. You know, stuff
that we've been able to do with all the
other image generation platforms for a
while now. Now, this is one of the other
ones that I thought was kind of cool.
And I believe we might have access to
this if you've updated to the beta
version of iOS 27, which is the spatial
reframing. You can take a picture like
he did on his phone here. And if he
doesn't like the framing, he can click
this little refframe button and then use
AI to change the framing and the angle
of the picture. And you can see the
little blurry parts are the parts that
were outside of the photo, but it's
going to use generative AI to fill in
those areas. But the portion of the
photo that is still clear is not using
generative AI. And I feel like those
were the main like big announcements to
come out of WWDC this year. Now, if you
do have an iPhone and if you did upgrade
it to the beta of iOS 27, you can use
the refframe right now. So, if I open my
camera app and I take a picture of just
like what I see in my office right now,
let's look at this photo. Click on the
settings, click on tools, and you can
see I now have refframe down in the
bottom right. So, if I click on reframe,
it scans the photo. And now I can
actually drag this around and reframe
this photo. Now we can see that it's
like distorting my camera and you know
it will have some wonkiness. It's
obviously more designed to like reframe
people in the photo, but let's like
change the angle entirely. Click
refframe and now it's going to generate
what it thinks the edges should look
like. So there you go. And that's
available in beta right now. One thing
to note about all of these Apple AI
announcements is they said they won't
initially be available in the EU due to
their AI restrictions there. They are
hoping to figure that out as quickly as
possible, but at launch they won't be
available. Moving on, Google had a
series of announcements this week that
if they weren't overshadowed by
Anthropic and Apple, would probably be
the biggest announcements of the week.
Let's start with the fact that Notebook
LM got a bit of an overhaul this week.
It was upgraded to run on the Gemini 3.5
model and each notebook is now equipped
with a secure cloud computer which
enables it to write and run code useful
for helping you perform deeper research
and more complex analysis. So there's
over 100 curated skills that now work
behind the scenes in Notebook LM
providing like a ton of new capabilities
within the platform. There's also new
formats that it can output. PNG and SVG,
PDFs, DOCX, Markdown, text files, PNG,
JPEG, GIF or GIF, CSV, JSON, XLSX, PPTX,
and you can even make edits after your
outputs are generated. It's gotten
better at research. You can actually now
start with loose ideas and questions,
and Notebook LM will guide you through
building your source repository directly
in the chat. Now, on the surface, when I
log into Notebook LM, I don't notice a
real huge difference. But it's when you
actually start chatting with it, you'll
notice that it's using a much better
model and that it can actually use
skills while you're chatting with it.
Create a chart that shows the growth of
the birds aren't real movement. We can
see it now says confirming tool use and
crafting the visual. And it kicked off
the infographic tool over here on the
right. And here's the chart that it
generated for me. Not quite what I was
asking, but uh you know, it took its own
liberties. But Google also showed off
their new Gemini 3.5 live translate
model which does exactly what it sounds
like. It will actually translate
conversations in near real time. Here's
the example they showed off.
>> Watch as we listen to the Google IO
keynote in Hindi.
>> What's really incredible is how people
are using our AI.
I think you get the idea. It's pretty
much like real time. You can watch a
video and have it translate for you in
real time. And it's actually coming to
Google Meet. So, you'll be able to have
meetings with people in other languages
directly inside of Google Meet pretty
soon.
>> Cassie, how's the weather in Shanghai?
It's nice to meet you. The weather here
is really nice. I spent the whole day
with my family in the park.
>> That sounds wonderful.
>> So, that should pretty much eliminate
all language barriers on meetings and
videos online. It's also coming to the
Google Translate app on Android and iOS
and you should be able to play with it
right now over inside of AI
Studio.google.com.
So, if I come up here, click into the
playground, click into speech and music
here, you can see Gemini 3.5 live
translate preview. I could select this
and I can directly talk and it will
translate. Let's have it translate to
Hindi and I'll click talk. Hello
everyone. Don't forget to like and
subscribe to MattWolf on YouTube.
Namaste. Matt Walker YouTuber like or
subscribe.
>> I don't know how well that worked, but
you get the idea here. But I can also
share audio from a tab. So if I select a
target language here, let's do Spanish
and then share audio from a tab. I could
select my YouTube channel here. Press
play on this video.
And you can see that as I was watching
the video, it was translating it in real
time just on another tab. And that's
available right now over in AI Studio on
Google. And the other announcement that
Google made this week was this new
diffusion Gemma. And what's special
about this is it does text generation,
but it just does it really really fast.
It uses the same technology as the image
generation models. You know what? Stable
diffusion and midjourney and dolly. All
of these are using diffusion models
under the hood. Well, this is using that
same technology, but it's generating
text instead of images. We can see it's
not the most intelligent model in the
world. It's about as intelligent as
Gemma 412B, maybe slightly less
intelligent, but it just blows
everything out of the water on speed
based on tokens per second. Here we can
see in this example here where it's
doing the Sudoku board, how quickly it
solved this right side versus it still
working on this left side. So, it's
speed that this is really, really good
at. So, here's the quick explanation of
what this is and why you might want to
use it. Most language models act like a
typewriter, generating one token at a
time from left to right. In the cloud,
this is efficient because servers can
batch thousands of users requests
together to share the hardware load. But
when run locally for a single user, this
word-by-word process leaves your
dedicated GPU or TPU underutilized. It
spends most of its time just waiting for
the next keystroke. Diffusion Gemma
reverses this inefficiency. Instead of
predicting words sequentially, it drafts
an entire 256 token paragraph
simultaneously by giving the computer's
processor a larger chunk of work at
once. Diffusion Gemma utilizes your
hardware to its full potential. So when
you start using a lot of these models on
your own computer more and more models
like these diffusion models are going to
use your own hardware much more
efficiently. And honestly, I think
that's the way things are going. And I
think more and more people are going to
want to figure out how to run AI models
on device without sending them to
clouds, without sending their data to
big companies that might train on them
or use them to target advertising to you
and things like that. So models like
this show that companies like Google are
actively thinking about how do we get
better models on your own home device.
All right, I know I've covered a lot.
It's been a big week, but I have a few
more smaller things that I want to talk
to you about real quick. So, let's just
jump into a rapid fire and I'll cover
them super quick.
Let's start with two different articles
penned by well, two of the biggest name
CEOs in the AI space right now. Daario
put out an article this week called
policy on the AI exponential and Sam
Alman and Jacob Pachokei put out this
article called built to benefit
everyone, our plan. Two sort of articles
laying out how these two companies see
the next phase of AI. Now, Daario's
article, the main sort of thesis of it
is that we're approaching what he's
calling powerful AI, or in other words,
a country of geniuses in a data center.
Now, this is a super long article here,
so I'm going to give you the TLDDR.
Daario argues that we need like an FAA
style regulatory body that reviews these
models before the public gets access to
them to make sure they're safe and
secure. He believes that there will
continue to be this hyper growth in the
economy, but we need to make sure that
everybody shares in on that wealth. He
acknowledges there will be job losses
and also suggests that something like a
UBI and actual higher taxes on the AI
companies that get distributed is one
way to sort of solve this. He talks
about how we can have huge advancements
in drug discoveries, but that the
current biomedical pipeline is too slow
and that we should figure out ways to
sort of speed up the process and let AI
take over a lot of it. As we've heard in
the past, he's worried about domestic
surveillance, autonomous weapons, things
like that, and that we need an off
switch for these models just in case
things do get out of hand. And he
suggests that we need some sort of like
international coalition all working
together to secure AI because any one
country being too far advanced is like
having a modern military but in medieval
times. So he's calling upon sort of
international collaboration to solve for
this. Now on to the article from Sam and
Jacob. This article is a little less
long, a little less dense, but here's
the TLDDR anyway. They believe that by
March 2028, we may have a significant
fraction of their research being done by
AI systems in tandem with researchers.
They also believe the economy is going
to accelerate by accelerating scientific
progress, productivity, and economic
growth. And they also say that they're
working to ensure gains are widely
shared. Everyone should have an
opportunity for meaningful share in the
prosperity AI creates. The sentiment
shared by both CEOs. They want to give
everyone on Earth a personal AGI,
empowering them to benefit from one of
humanity's most transformative
technologies in whatever way they
choose. They go on to say that they're
entering what they call the third phase
of open AI. The first phase was doing
research towards AGI. The second phase
was when the research became relevant
and you know basically useful to the
world chat GPT essentially. And now
we're on to the third phase. This is
where the economy is beginning to shape
itself around AI. But they go on to
reiterate that above all we believe a
broad distribution of power will help
lead to a better future. They want to
make sure it's accessible for all. And
they also believe safety, privacy,
affordability, open ecosystems, and
public oversight matter. A good AI
future cannot be one where a small
number of institutions control most of
the capability and most of the upside.
They believe the transformation should
belong to everyone. Very similar
messages, one a little bit longer, one a
little bit more brief, but coming from
both of the most dominant AI labs of the
moment. All right, those were a little
less rapid fire fiery than I wanted them
to be. The rest will be really quick, I
promise. ChatGpt rolled out a new
feature where you can actually send
emails directly from with inside of
ChatGpt. So, you can have it craft an
email. You plug in the email address
that it's going to and you can send it
directly from within the chat app. We
have a couple announcements around IPOs.
Open AAI filed for an IPO. We don't
actually know when this IPO is going to
happen. It's probably still a ways off
honestly if I had to guess. We'll see
the OpenAI IPO like next year, early
next year sometime, but they did file.
So, they're showing their intention to
IPO soon. But since we're talking about
IPOs, as of this video going live,
SpaceX has officially IPOed. Now, as of
the recording, they raised $75 billion
in a record-breaking IPO, but this is,
you know, before the official listing on
the market where people can start
trading it. So, by the time this video
is live, people can actively trade
SpaceX on the market. At the time of
this recording, they sold 555 million
plus shares for $135 a piece, making the
valuation 1.77 trillion, but again, as
of the time this video is actually live,
the valuation of this company is now up
to the open markets. Coinbase is making
their platform available for your
agents. So, now your AI agent can trade
and pay with Coinbase. So, if you feel
comfortable enough giving your OpenClaw
or Hermes agent or whatever agent of
choice you're using access to your
Coinbase account, apparently you can do
that now. And finally, we got this tweet
from David Holtz, who is the founder of
Midjourney, and they're kind of teasing
there's some sort of like physical
gadget coming. We're starting to send
out invites for our first MidJourney
hardware launch, and I feel like I'm
missing some important mutuals. Poke me
if you haven't gotten an invite and
think you should. I have no idea what
this means, but apparently Midjourney is
releasing some sort of hardware in the
near future, so that could be
interesting. Still no clue what it is,
but we'll see. If you have ideas, let me
know in the comments. Whatever it is,
I'm sure I'll probably end up buying it.
Anyway, that's what I got for you. I
record these videos on Thursdays,
publish them on Friday. So, if there's
any news that I missed that came out
like late Thursday night or on Friday,
it didn't make this video, but I'll make
sure it makes it into next week's video.
There is a lot happening in the world of
AI every single day. There's new
announcements. There's so many new tools
to test and models coming out that are
supposedly better and YouTube channels
and Twitter accounts that are hyping up
everything is like this business is
cooked or this model just changed the
game or if you're not using this agent
then you're falling behind. And so much
of it is hype. And so it is my goal with
this channel to cut through all the
noise, cut through all the hype and
share with you just the things I think
are most important for the most amount
of people to know. I'll drink from the
fire hose. I'll be overwhelmed all week
and then I'll turn around and break it
down for you on these Friday videos so
you can just watch one video a week if
you want and get totally looped in on
everything you need to know. I'm also
going to throw in some, you know,
tutorials and cool ways to use some of
those tools in between the news videos,
but these news videos, you can count on
them pretty much every Friday. If that's
something that interests you, maybe
consider liking and subscribing to this
channel, and I'll make sure more videos
like this show up in your YouTube feed.
But again, that's what I got for you.
It's been a very hectic week. A really
cool model in Fable. I'm having a lot of
fun using Fable to generate games and
apps that make my editing life easier.
And uh yeah, you should go try them out.
They're pretty cool. Anyway, again,
thanks for nerding out with me. Thanks
for hanging out with me. I'm done
rambling. Hopefully, I'll see you in the
next one. Bye-bye.